<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<quotes>
	<quote id="1" author="soyen">So many people love you. Don't focus on the people who don't</quote>
	<quote id="2" author="Unknown">Don't let little stupid things break your happiness</quote>
	<quote id="3" author="Unknown">You deserve a life full of happiness and positivity</quote>
	<quote id="4" author="Unknown">Always be a little kinder than necessary</quote>
	<quote id="5" author="Unknown">Be so happy that when others look at you, they become happy too</quote>
	<quote id="6" author="Debby Ryan">Decorate your life with hearts that make yours stronger</quote>
	<quote id="7" author="faraway">Being happy with yourself is the best kind of happiness</quote>
	<quote id="8" author="Audrey Hepburn">The most important thing is to enjoy your life — to be happy — it’s all that matters</quote>
	<quote id="9" author="Unknown">Start your day with positive thoughts</quote>
	<quote id="10" author="Nicole Addison">You deserve to laugh. To be happy. To live a joyful life. You deserve to experience moments of pure beauty and bliss</quote>
	<quote id="11" author="Unknown">Life is only as good as your mindset</quote>
	<quote id="12" author="Unknown">Choose your happiness over everything</quote>
	<quote id="13" author="Unknown">Don't stop until you're proud</quote>
	<quote id="14" author="Unknown">Never regret a day in your life: good days give happiness, bad days give experience, worst days give lessons, and best days give memories</quote>
	<quote id="15" author="Unknown">Very little is needed to make a happy life</quote>
	<quote id="16" author="Unknown">Start each day with a grateful heart</quote>
	<quote id="17" author="Unknown">Next time when you think of beautiful things, don't forget to count yourself in</quote>
	<quote id="18" author="Unknown">You &gt; The World</quote>
	<quote id="19" author="Unknown">Don't fill your head with worries, there won't be room for anything else!</quote>
	<quote id="20" author="Unknown">A positive mind will give you a positive life</quote>
	<quote id="21" author="Unknown">Be honest with yourself</quote>
	<quote id="22" author="Unknown">You don’t deserve a paragraph. You deserve a thousand books written about how amazing you are</quote>
	<quote id="23" author="John Zabat-Zinn">The little things? The little moments? They aren’t little</quote>
	<quote id="24" author="Susan Polis Schutz">Let us dance in the sun, wearing wild flowers in our hair...</quote>
	<quote id="25" author="Mark Anthony">I want you to be happy because you deserve it. I want you to be happy, because it makes me happy to see you, the way you were meant to be</quote>
	<quote id="26" author="Thich Nhat Hanh">Walk as if you are kissing the Earth with your feet</quote>
	<quote id="27" author="Francisca Alves">The only thing that stops you is you</quote>
	<quote id="28" author="Unknown">A smile does not waste electricity, and generates much more light</quote>
	<quote id="29" author="Unknown">There will always be someone who thinks you can't succeed. Make sure that someone isn't you</quote>
	<quote id="30" author="Walt Disney">It's kind of fun to do the impossible</quote>
	<quote id="31" author="Walt Disney">All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them</quote>
	<quote id="32" author="Walt Disney">The more you like yourself, the less you are like anyone else, which makes you unique</quote>
	<quote id="33" author="Frank Tyger">Doing what you like is freedom. Liking what you do is happiness</quote>
	<quote id="34" author="Kareena Kapoor Khan">Life is full of happiness and tears; be strong and have faith</quote>
	<quote id="35" author="Jim Rohn">Happiness is not something you postpone for the future; it is something you design for the present</quote>
	<quote id="36" author="Susan Cain">Spend your free time the way you like, not the way you think you’re supposed to</quote>
	<quote id="37" author="São Fernandes">Thoughts are real actions, be careful to choose the best ones</quote>
	<quote id="38" author="Unknown">Happiness comes when you find meaning in your life. If that envolve helping other people, even better</quote>
	<quote id="39" author="Unknown">We just have one shot at life and you are the person that is gonna decide how the journey will be</quote>
	<quote id="40" author="Henry Ford">Failure is simply the opportunity to begin again, this time more intelligently</quote>
	<quote id="41" author="Unknown">You don't know how lovely you are</quote>
	<quote id="42" author="Unknown">If you think you can, you will</quote>
	<quote id="43" author="Unknown">Life is short. If there was ever a moment to follow your passion and do something that matters to you, that moment is now!</quote>
	<quote id="44" author="Unknown">Mental health first, everything else will follow</quote>
	<quote id="45" author="Unknown">Be patient. The best things happen unexpectedly</quote>
	<quote id="46" author="Unknown">Never regret anything that once made you smile</quote>
	<quote id="47" author="Unknown">A small act of kindness creates the greatest of joys</quote>
	<quote id="48" author="soyen">And they keep asking me where happiness can be found, but I'm no longer trying to find happiness I just appreciate where I am and then happiness finds me</quote>
	<quote id="49" author="Unknown">Be kind to yourself!</quote>
	<quote id="50" author="Unknown">You are lovely</quote>
	<quote id="51" author="Unknown">Don't just be good to others. Be good to yourself!</quote>
	<quote id="52" author="Unknown">Smile!</quote>
	<quote id="53" author="Unknown">If it makes you happy, it doesn't have to make sense to others</quote>
	<quote id="54" author="Nike">Yesterday, you said tomorrow</quote>
	<quote id="55" author="Jon Acuff">Don't compare your beginning to someone else's middle</quote>
	<quote id="56" author="George Santayana">The wisest mind has something yet to learn</quote>
	<quote id="57" author="Mahatma Gandhi">Be the change you wish to see in the world</quote>
	<quote id="58" author="Winston Churchill">When you're going through hell, keep going</quote>
	<quote id="59" author="Danielle LaPorte">Don't let perfection become procrastination. Do it now</quote>
	<quote id="60" author="Danielle LaPorte">Launch and learn. Everything is progress</quote>
	<quote id="61" author="Karen Lamb">A year from now you will wish you had started today</quote>
	<quote id="62" author="Unknown">Failure is success if you learn from it</quote>
	<quote id="63" author="Jim Rohn">If you don't like where you are, change it. You're not a tree</quote>
	<quote id="64" author="Jack Canfield">If it ain't fun, don't do it</quote>
	<quote id="65" author="Risa Rodil">A wet man does not fear the rain</quote>
	<quote id="66" author="Whole Earth Epilog">Stay hungry; stay foolish</quote>
	<quote id="67" author="Paul Carus">No one saves us but ourselves. No one can and no one may. We ourselves must walk the path</quote>
	<quote id="68" author="Unknown">Never give up. Never let things out of your control dictate who you are</quote>
	<quote id="69" author="Ian Maclaren">Be kind; everyone you meet is fighting a hard battle</quote>
	<quote id="70" author="Muhammed Ali">Impossible is just a big word thrown around by small men who find it easier to live in the world they've been given than to explore the power they have to change it</quote>
	<quote id="71" author="Andrew Carnegie">People who are unable to motivate themselves must be content with mediocrity no matter how impressive their other talents</quote>
	<quote id="72" author="George Bernard Shaw">Progress is impossible without change, and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything</quote>
	<quote id="73" author="Carmel McConnell">Do more of what makes you happy</quote>
	<quote id="74" author="Unknown">Do a little more of what you want to do every day, until your idea becomes what's real</quote>
	<quote id="75" author="Danielle LaPorte">You got this. Make it happen</quote>
	<quote id="76" author="Unknown">Don't blame others as an excuse for your not working hard enough</quote>
	<quote id="77" author="Lao Tzu">Care about what other people think and you will always be their prisoner</quote>
	<quote id="78" author="Elbert Hubbard">To escape criticism: do nothing, say nothing, be nothing</quote>
	<quote id="79" author="Elbert Hubbard">The world is moving so fast that the man who says it can't be done is generally interrupted by someone doing it</quote>
	<quote id="80" author="Dr. Seuss">Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter and those who matter don't mind</quote>
	<quote id="81" author="Paulo Coelho">One day you will wake up and there won't be any more time to do the things you've always wanted. Do it now</quote>
	<quote id="82" author="Dwight D. Eisenhower">Never waste a minute thinking about people you don't like</quote>
	<quote id="83" author="Unknown">Never let your fear decide your fate</quote>
	<quote id="84" author="Unknown">Keep moving forward. One step at a time</quote>
	<quote id="85" author="Unknown">Life is simple. Are you happy? Yes? Keep going. No? Change something</quote>
	<quote id="86" author="Unknown">The journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step</quote>
	<quote id="87" author="Nicholas Klein">First they ignore you. Then they laugh at you. Then they fight you. Then you win</quote>
	<quote id="88" author="Mahatma Gandhi">A man is but the product of his thoughts. What he thinks, he becomes</quote>
	<quote id="89" author="Unknown">Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever</quote>
	<quote id="90" author="Mahatma Gandhi">The future depends on what we do in the present</quote>
	<quote id="91" author="Unknown">I am strong because I've been weak. I am fearless because I've been afraid. I am wise because I've been foolish</quote>
	<quote id="92" author="Unknown">Believe in yourself</quote>
	<quote id="93" author="Unknown">Lower the cost of failure</quote>
	<quote id="94" author="Peter McWilliams">Keep your goals away from the trolls</quote>
	<quote id="95" author="Robert Tew">Respect yourself enough to walk away from anything that no longer serves you, grows you, or makes you happy</quote>
	<quote id="96" author="Unknown">Everything around you, that you call life, was made up by people, and you can change it!</quote>
	<quote id="97" author="Eric Hoffer">In times of change, learners inherit the earth, while the learned find themselves beautifully equipped to deal with a world that no longer exists</quote>
	<quote id="98" author="Unknown">If you fear failure, you will never go anywhere</quote>
	<quote id="99" author="Unknown">Go ahead, let them judge you</quote>
	<quote id="100" author="Unknown">The world breaks everyone and afterward many are strong at the broken places</quote>
	<quote id="101" author="Matthew Jeffers">The only disability in life is a bad attitude</quote>
	<quote id="102" author="Albert Einstein">If most of us are ashamed of shabby clothes and shoddy furniture, let us be more ashamed of shabby ideas and shoddy philosophies</quote>
	<quote id="103" author="J. Krishnamurti">It is no measure of health to be well adjusted to a profoundly sick society</quote>
	<quote id="104" author="Miyamoto Musashi">Think lightly of yourself and deeply of the world</quote>
	<quote id="105" author="Jake the Dog">Dude, suckin' at something is the first step to being sorta good at something</quote>
	<quote id="106" author="Unknown">As you think, so shall you become</quote>
	<quote id="107" author="Bruce Lee">Do not wish for an easy life. Wish for the strength to endure a difficult one</quote>
	<quote id="108" author="Bruce Lee">Showing off is the fool's idea of glory</quote>
	<quote id="109" author="Bruce Lee">Use only that which works, and take it from any place you can find it</quote>
	<quote id="110" author="Bruce Lee">I'm not in this world to live up to your expectations and you're not in this world to live up to mine</quote>
	<quote id="111" author="Bruce Lee">If you spend too much time thinking about a thing, you'll never get it done</quote>
	<quote id="112" author="Bruce Lee">Knowing is not enough, we must apply. Willing is not enough, we must do</quote>
	<quote id="113" author="Bruce Lee">Empty your cup so that it may be filled; become devoid to gain totality</quote>
	<quote id="114" author="Bruce Lee">It's not the daily increase but daily decrease. Hack away at the unessential</quote>
	<quote id="115" author="Oscar Wilde">Be yourself. Everyone else is already taken</quote>
	<quote id="116" author="Martin Luther King Jr.">Darkness cannot drive out darkness; only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate; only love can do that</quote>
	<quote id="117" author="Bil Keane">Yesterday is history; tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift, which is why we call it the present</quote>
	<quote id="118" author="Albert Einstein">Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world</quote>
	<quote id="119" author="Thomas Edison">I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work</quote>
	<quote id="120" author="Unknown">When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be</quote>
	<quote id="121" author="George Eliot">It is never too late to be what you might have been</quote>
	<quote id="122" author="Bruce Lee">Always be yourself, express yourself, have faith in yourself. Do not go out and look for a successful personality and duplicate it</quote>
	<quote id="123" author="Lao Tzu">When you are content to be simply yourself and don't compare or compete, everyone will respect you</quote>
	<quote id="124" author="Lao Tzu">If you want to awaken all of humanity, awaken all of yourself</quote>
	<quote id="125" author="Unknown">Don't regret anything you do, because in the end it makes you who you are</quote>
	<quote id="126" author="Unknown">Tension is who you think you should be. Relaxation is who you are</quote>
	<quote id="127" author="Unknown">You are confined only by the walls you build yourself</quote>
	<quote id="128" author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">Unless you try to do something beyond what you have already mastered you will never grow</quote>
	<quote id="129" author="Unknown">Don't think about what might go wrong, think about what could be right</quote>
	<quote id="130" author="Lao Tzu">What the caterpillar calls the end, the rest of the world calls a butterfly</quote>
	<quote id="131" author="Thich Nhat Hanh">To be beautiful means to be yourself. You don't need to be accepted by others. You need to be yourself</quote>
	<quote id="132" author="Unknown">Let go of those who bring you down and surround yourself with those who bring out the best in you</quote>
	<quote id="133" author="Unknown">Don't let small minds convince you that your dreams are too big</quote>
	<quote id="134" author="Maya Angelou">If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude. Don't complain</quote>
	<quote id="135" author="Maya Angelou">You may not control all the events that happen to you, but you can decide not to be reduced by them</quote>
	<quote id="136" author="Maya Angelou">I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back</quote>
	<quote id="137" author="Maya Angelou">I don't trust people who don't love themselves and tell me, 'I love you.' There is an African saying which is: 'Be careful when a naked person offers you a shirt.'</quote>
	<quote id="138" author="Maya Angelou">People will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel</quote>
	<quote id="139" author="Arnold Schwarzenegger">You can't climb the ladder of success with your hands in your pockets</quote>
	<quote id="140" author="Unknown">You can feel sore tomorrow or you can feel sorry tomorrow. You choose</quote>
	<quote id="141" author="Isocrates">It is more important to know where you are going than to get there quickly. Do not mistake activity for achievement</quote>
	<quote id="142" author="Unknown">There are seven days in the week and someday isn't one of them</quote>
	<quote id="143" author="Arthur Ashe">Start where you are. Use what you can. Do what you can</quote>
	<quote id="144" author="Unknown">Dreams don't work unless you do</quote>
	<quote id="145" author="Unknown">When you wake up in the morning you have two choices: go back to sleep, or wake up and chase those dreams</quote>
	<quote id="146" author="Unknown">Everybody comes to a point in their life when they want to quit, but it's what you do at that moment that determines who you are</quote>
	<quote id="147" author="Unknown">This is your life. Do what you love, and do it often</quote>
	<quote id="148" author="Unknown">Live your dream, and wear your passion</quote>
	<quote id="149" author="Unknown">Today I will do what others won't, so tomorrow I can do what others can't</quote>
	<quote id="150" author="Unknown">The biggest room in the world is room for improvement</quote>
	<quote id="151" author="Unknown">If people aren't laughing at your dreams, your dreams aren't big enough</quote>
	<quote id="152" author="Unknown">Never look back unless you are planning to go that way</quote>
	<quote id="153" author="Unknown">Every dream begins with a dreamer. Always remember, you have within you the strength, the patience, and the passion to reach for the stars to change the world</quote>
	<quote id="154" author="Unknown">You are awesome</quote>
	<quote id="155" author="Unknown">Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication</quote>
	<quote id="156" author="Henry Ford">Anyone who stops learning is old</quote>
	<quote id="157" author="Unknown">The cure to boredom is curiosity</quote>
	<quote id="158" author="Unknown">Never give up on a dream just because of the time it will take to accomplish it. The time will pass anyway</quote>
	<quote id="159" author="Unknown">It's time to start living the life you've only imagined</quote>
	<quote id="160" author="Unknown">You don't have to live your life the way other people expect you to</quote>
	<quote id="161" author="Unknown">The trouble with not having a goal is that you can spend your life running up and down the field and never score</quote>
	<quote id="162" author="Unknown">To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment</quote>
	<quote id="163" author="Unknown">Incredible change happens in your life when you decide to take control of what you do have power over instead of craving control over what you don't</quote>
	<quote id="164" author="Unknown">Do more with less</quote>
	<quote id="165" author="Unknown">Overthinking ruins you. Ruins the situation, twists it around, makes you worry and just makes everything much worse than it actually is</quote>
	<quote id="166" author="Unknown">Replace fear of the unknown with curiosity</quote>
	<quote id="167" author="Unknown">The surest way to find your dream job is to create it</quote>
	<quote id="168" author="Unknown">What you do today is important because you are exchanging a day of your life for it</quote>
	<quote id="169" author="Unknown">One man or woman with courage is a majority</quote>
	<quote id="170" author="Eleanor Roosevelt">Do one thing every day that scares you</quote>
	<quote id="171" author="Unknown">Don't just wait for inspiration. Become it</quote>
	<quote id="172" author="Unknown">Don't limit your challenges - challenge your limits</quote>
	<quote id="173" author="Wayne Dyer">When you judge others, you do not define them; you define yourself</quote>
	<quote id="174" author="Unknown">Time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time</quote>
	<quote id="175" author="Mother Teresa">Do small things with great love</quote>
	<quote id="176" author="Unknown">Go forth and make awesomeness</quote>
	<quote id="177" author="Napolean Hill">Your big opportunity may be right where you are now</quote>
	<quote id="178" author="Unknown">Life begins at the end of your comfort zone</quote>
	<quote id="179" author="Unknown">Excuses are born out of fear. Eliminate your fear and there will be no excuses</quote>
	<quote id="180" author="Unknown">Happiness is not the absence of problems, it's the ability to deal with them</quote>
	<quote id="181" author="Unknown">The problem is not the problem. The problem is your attitude about the problem</quote>
	<quote id="182" author="Unknown">You don't have to be great to start, but you have to start to be great</quote>
	<quote id="183" author="Unknown">Cherish your visions and your dreams as they are the children of your soul, the blueprints of your ultimate achievements</quote>
	<quote id="184" author="Unknown">Decide that you want it more than you are afraid of it</quote>
	<quote id="185" author="Unknown">Adventure may hurt you, but monotony will kill you</quote>
	<quote id="186" author="Unknown">Obsessed is a word that the lazy use to describe the dedicated</quote>
	<quote id="187" author="Unknown">If they can do it, so can you</quote>
	<quote id="188" author="Unknown">Success isn't about being the best. It's about always getting better</quote>
	<quote id="189" author="Winston Churchill">Success is the ability to go from failure to failure without losing your enthusiasm</quote>
	<quote id="190" author="Winston Churchill">A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty</quote>
	<quote id="191" author="Unknown">Failure is just practice for success</quote>
	<quote id="192" author="Unknown">Shipping beats perfection</quote>
	<quote id="193" author="Seneca">While we are postponing, life speeds by</quote>
	<quote id="194" author="Nelson Mandela">It always seems impossible until it's done</quote>
	<quote id="195" author="Zig Ziglar">Don't let the mistakes and disappointments of the past control and direct your future</quote>
	<quote id="196" author="Unknown">It's not about where your starting point is, but your end goal and the journey that will get you there</quote>
	<quote id="197" author="Marcus Aurelius">Waste no more time arguing about what a good person should be. Be one</quote>
	<quote id="198" author="Anaïs Nin">Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage</quote>
	<quote id="199" author="Bruce Lee">Absorb what is useful. Discard what is not. Add what is uniquely your own</quote>
	<quote id="200" author="Henry Ford">Don't find fault. Find a remedy</quote>
	<quote id="201" author="Karim Seddiki">Doubt kills more dreams than failure ever will</quote>
	<quote id="202" author="Zig Ziglar">Don't let someone who gave up on their dreams talk you out of going after yours</quote>
	<quote id="203" author="Dean Acheson">Always remember that the future comes one day at a time</quote>
	<quote id="204" author="Ursula K. Le Guin">The creative adult is the child who survived</quote>
	<quote id="205" author="Thomas Edison">When you have exhausted all possibilities, remember this: you haven't</quote>
	<quote id="206" author="Zig Ziglar">When you see a person without a smile, give them one of yours</quote>
	<quote id="207" author="Vincent Van Gogh">If you hear a voice within you say 'you cannot paint,' then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced</quote>
	<quote id="208" author="Thucydides">The secret to happiness is freedom. And the secret to freedom is courage</quote>
	<quote id="209" author="Nelson Mandela">May your choices reflect your hopes, not your fears</quote>
	<quote id="210" author="Dalai Lama">Once a year, go some place you've never been before</quote>
	<quote id="211" author="Margaret Meade">Never underestimate the ability of a small group of dedicated people to change the world. Indeed, it is the only thing that ever has</quote>
	<quote id="212" author="Nelson Mandela">To be free is not merely to cast off one's chains, but to live in a way that respects and enhances the freedom of others</quote>
	<quote id="213" author="Thich Nhat Hanh">Today is the most important day of our lives</quote>
	<quote id="214" author="Maya Angelou">All great achievements require time</quote>
	<quote id="215" author="Unknown">Winning starts with beginning</quote>
	<quote id="216" author="Unknown">If you're not doing what you love, you're wasting your time</quote>
	<quote id="217" author="Bruce Lee">A goal is not always meant to be reached, it often serves simply as something to aim at</quote>
	<quote id="218" author="Unknown">The struggle ends when the gratitude begins</quote>
	<quote id="219" author="Alan Watts">Muddy water is best cleared by leaving it alone</quote>
	<quote id="220" author="Eric Hoffer">Someone who thinks the world is always cheating him is right. He is missing that wonderful feeling of trust in someone or something</quote>
	<quote id="221" author="Galileo Galilei">We cannot teach people anything. We can only help them discover it within themselves</quote>
	<quote id="222" author="Annie Dillard">How we spend our days is, of course, how we spend our lives</quote>
	<quote id="223" author="Vincent Van Gogh">I would rather die of passion than of boredom</quote>
	<quote id="224" author="Laird Hamilton">Make sure your worst enemy doesn't live between your two ears</quote>
	<quote id="225" author="Maya Angelou">You can't use up creativity. The more you use the more you have</quote>
	<quote id="226" author="Unknown">The secret of change is to focus all of your energy, not on fighting the old but on building the new</quote>
	<quote id="227" author="Peter Drucker">Whenever you see a successful business, someone once made a courageous decision</quote>
	<quote id="228" author="Unknown">If you stumble make it part of the dance</quote>
	<quote id="229" author="Unknown">Each day wake up and ask yourself what will make you feel most alive that day</quote>
	<quote id="230" author="Confucius">Choose a job you love and you will never have to work a day of your life</quote>
	<quote id="231" author="Lou Holtz">It is not the load that breaks you down. It's the way you carry it</quote>
	<quote id="232" author="Unknown">If you want to go fast, go alone. If you want to go far, bring others along</quote>
	<quote id="233" author="Sir Ken Robinson">Children are wonderfully confident in their own imaginations. Most of us lose this confidence as we grow up</quote>
	<quote id="234" author="Jean Luc Picard">It is possible to commit no mistakes and still lose. That is not a weakness; that is life</quote>
	<quote id="235" author="Nelson Mandela">So many of our dreams at first seem impossible. Then they seem improbable. And then, when we summon the will, they soon become inevitable</quote>
	<quote id="236" author="Greg McKeown">If you don't prioritize your life, someone else will</quote>
	<quote id="237" author="Richard Bach">Argue for your limitations, and surely they're yours</quote>
	<quote id="238" author="David Burns">There is only one person who could ever make you happy, and that person is you</quote>
	<quote id="239" author="Unknown">A goal without a plan is only a wish</quote>
	<quote id="240" author="Six Degrees of Separation">Every person is a new door to a different world</quote>
	<quote id="241" author="Unknown">On your journey through life, make sure your biography has at least one extraordinary chapter</quote>
	<quote id="242" author="Steve Jobs">The journey is the reward</quote>
	<quote id="243" author="Buddha">Know well what leads you forward and what holds you back, and choose the path that leads you to wisdom</quote>
	<quote id="244" author="Pablo Picasso">The meaning of life is to find your gift. The purpose of life is to give it away</quote>
	<quote id="245" author="Stephen McCranie">The master has failed more times than the beginner has even tried</quote>
	<quote id="246" author="Savas Dimopoulos">Jumping from failure to failure with undiminished enthusiasm is the big secret to success</quote>
	<quote id="247" author="Naguib Mahfouz">Fear does not prevent death. It prevents life</quote>
	<quote id="248" author="Vincent Van Gogh">Great things are done by a series of small things brought together</quote>
	<quote id="249" author="Walt Disney">The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing</quote>
	<quote id="250" author="Karen Salmansohn">What are the most powerful words in the universe? The ones you use to talk to yourself</quote>
	<quote id="251" author="Hermann Hesse">Within you is a stillness and a sanctuary to which you can retreat at any time and be yourself</quote>
	<quote id="252" author="Richard Branson">Spend more time smiling than frowning and more time praising than criticizing</quote>
	<quote id="253" author="Jim Rohn">Success is something you attract by the person you become</quote>
	<quote id="254" author="A. A. Milne">Always remember you are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think</quote>
	<quote id="255" author="Winnie the Pooh">Don't underestimate the value of doing nothing, of just going along, listening to all the things you can't hear, and not bothering</quote>
	<quote id="256" author="Merlin">It's up to you how far you go. If you don't try, you'll never know!</quote>
	<quote id="257" author="Archimedes">The only way to learn it is to do it</quote>
	<quote id="258" author="Unknown">In matters of style swim with the current. In matters of principle, stand like a rock</quote>
	<quote id="259" author="C. S. Lewis">You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream</quote>
	<quote id="260" author="Mahatma Gandhi">Whenever you are confronted with an opponent, conquer him with love</quote>
	<quote id="261" author="Steve Jobs">The only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle</quote>
	<quote id="262" author="Alexandra K. Trenfor">The best teachers are those who show you where to look, but don't tell you what to see</quote>
	<quote id="263" author="Henry David Thoreau">It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see</quote>
	<quote id="264" author="Immanuel Kant">Rules for happiness: something to do, someone to love, something to hope for</quote>
	<quote id="265" author="Karen Salmansohn">When feeling overwhelmed by a faraway goal, repeat the following: I have it within me right now, to get me to where I want to be later</quote>
	<quote id="266" author="Roald Dahl">If you have good thoughts they will shine out of your face like sunbeams and you will always look lovely</quote>
	<quote id="267" author="Marcus Aurelius">You have power over your mind -- not outside events. Realize this, and you will find strength</quote>
	<quote id="268" author="Jonathan Safran Foer">You cannot protect yourself from sadness without protecting yourself from happiness</quote>
	<quote id="269" author="William James">Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does</quote>
	<quote id="270" author="Khalil Gibran">Progress lies not in enhancing what is, but in advancing toward what will be</quote>
	<quote id="271" author="Matsuo Basho">Sitting quietly, doing nothing, Spring comes, and the grass grows by itself</quote>
	<quote id="272" author="Carlos Drummond de Andrade">Be happy for no reason is the most authentic form of happiness</quote>
	<quote id="273" author="Luís Ferreira">Put a smile on your face and go for it!</quote>
	<quote id="274" author="André Ramos">Happiness isn't the reason, the reason is you!</quote>
	<quote id="275" author="Unknown">You're such a beautiful person.</quote>
	<quote id="276" author="Ashley Montagu">The moments of happiness we enjoy take us by surprise. It is not that we seize them, but that they seize us.</quote>
	<quote id="277" author="Cesare Pavese">The only joy in the world is to begin.</quote>
	<quote id="278" author="Seneca">It is more fitting for a man to laugh at life than to lament over it.</quote>
	<quote id="279" author="James M. Barrie">The secret of happiness is not in doing what one likes, but in liking what one does.</quote>
	<quote id="280" author="Dr. Robert Anthony">Most people would rather be certain they’re miserable, than risk being happy.</quote>
	<quote id="281" author="Confucius">Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated.</quote>
	<quote id="282" author="James Oppenheim">The foolish man seeks happiness in the distance, the wise grows it under his feet.</quote>
	<quote id="283" author="Martha Washington">The greater part of our happiness or misery depends upon our dispositions, and not upon our circumstances.</quote>
	<quote id="284" author="Unknown">You're such a talented person.</quote>
	<quote id="285" author="Albert Ellis">The best years of your life are the ones in which you decide your problems are your own. You do not blame them on your mother, the ecology, or the president. You realize that you control your own destiny.</quote>
	<quote id="286" author="Unknown">Just because it didn’t last forever, doesn’t mean it wasn’t worth your while.</quote>
	<quote id="287" author="Maxim Gorky">Happiness always looks small while you hold it in your hands, but let it go, and you learn at once how big and precious it is</quote>
	<quote id="288" author="F. Scott Fitzgerald">It was only a sunny smile, and little it cost in the giving, but like morning light it scattered the night and made the day worth living.</quote>
	<quote id="289" author="William Feather">Plenty of people miss their share of happiness, not because they never found it, but because they didn’t stop to enjoy it.</quote>
	<quote id="290" author="Eleanor Roosevelt">No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.</quote>
	<quote id="291" author="Andy Rooney">For most of life, nothing wonderful happens. If you don’t enjoy getting up and working and finishing your work and sitting down to a meal with family or friends, then the chances are you’re not going to be very happy. If someone bases his/her happiness on major events like a great job, huge amounts of money, a flawlessly happy marriage or a trip to Paris, that person isn’t going to be happy much of the time. If, on the other hand, happiness depends on a good breakfast, flowers in the yard, a drink or a nap, then we are more likely to live with quite a bit of happiness.</quote>
	<quote id="292" author="Buddha">Learn to let go. That is the key to happiness.</quote>
	<quote id="293" author="Unknown">Admire someone else's beauty without questioning your own.</quote>
	<quote id="294" author="Unknown">When we deny our emotions, we become a slave to them. It's only when we acknowledge them that we can put them in their rightful place.</quote>
	<quote id="295" author="Unknown">So many years of education yet nobody ever taught us how to love ourselves and why it's important.</quote>
	<quote id="296" author="Unknown">It's better to love and lose than never love at all.</quote>
	<quote id="297" author="Unknown">Spend a little more time trying to make something of yourself and a little less time trying to impress people.</quote>
	<quote id="298" author="Unknown">Get piercings, remove them, make friends, move on, travel, stay in. Find what kind of person you are and love that person.</quote>
	<quote id="299" author="Unknown">Our purpose is never to get away from hard things. It's to find the hard things worth doing.</quote>
	<quote id="300" author="Unknown">Fill your life with adventures, not things. Have stories to tell, not stuff to show.</quote>
	<quote id="301" author="Unknown">Be strong, be weak, be whoever you want to be.</quote>
	<quote id="302" author="Unknown">You are enough.</quote>
	<quote id="303" author="Unknown">Do more things that make you forget to check your phone.</quote>
	<quote id="304" author="Unknown">Be soft. Do not let the world make you hard. Do not let pain make you hate. Do not let the bitterness steal your sweetness. Take pride that even though the rest of the world may disagree, you still believe it to be a beautiful place.</quote>
	<quote id="305" author="Unknown">Act as if it were impossible to fail.</quote>
	<quote id="306" author="Unknown">People wait all week for Friday, all year for summer, and all of life for happiness.</quote>
	<quote id="307" author="Unknown">Be the reason someone smiles today.</quote>
	<quote id="308" author="Unknown">Happiness looks good on you!</quote>
	<quote id="309" author="Unknown">The best view comes after the hardest climb.</quote>
	<quote id="310" author="Unknown">You were not born to just pay bills and die.</quote>
	<quote id="311" author="Unknown">Be who you needed when you were younger.</quote>
	<quote id="312" author="Unknown">Be a combination of all the best people you meet, not the worst.</quote>
	<quote id="313" author="Unknown">Stop being afraid of what could go wrong and start being positive about what could go right.</quote>
	<quote id="314" author="Unknown">A wolf does not lose sleep over the opinion of sheep.</quote>
	<quote id="315" author="Unknown">Be a Fruit Loop in a world of Cheerios.</quote>
	<quote id="316" author="L.R.Knost">Do not be dismayed by the brokenness of the world. All things break. And all things can be mended. Not with time, as they say, but with intention. So go. Love intentionally, extravagantly, unconditionally. The broken world waits in darkness for the light that is you.</quote>
	<quote id="317" author="Dr. Seuss">Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened.</quote>
	<quote id="318" author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness.</quote>
	<quote id="319" author="Robert A. Heinlein">Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own.</quote>
	<quote id="320" author="Abraham Lincoln">Folks are usually about as happy as they make their minds up to be.</quote>
	<quote id="321" author="Marthe Troly-Curtin">Time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time.</quote>
	<quote id="322" author="Chuck Palahniuk">It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness. We have no scar to show for happiness. We learn so little from peace.</quote>
	<quote id="323" author="George Sand">There is only one happiness in this life, to love and be loved.</quote>
	<quote id="324" author="Omar Khayyam">Be happy for this moment. This moment is your life.</quote>
	<quote id="325" author="Mahatma Gandhi">Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony.</quote>
	<quote id="326" author="Albert Camus">You will never be happy if you continue to search for what happiness consists of. You will never live if you are looking for the meaning of life.</quote>
	<quote id="327" author="Charles M. Schulz">Happiness is a warm puppy</quote>
	<quote id="328" author="William James">We don't laugh because we're happy – we're happy because we laugh.</quote>
	<quote id="329" author="Frida Kahlo">At the end of the day, we can endure much more than we think we can.</quote>
	<quote id="330" author="Unknown">There is always something to be thankful for.</quote>
	<quote id="331" author="Unknown">Try to love yourself as much as you want someone else to.</quote>
	<quote id="332" author="Unknown">Lets root for each other and watch each other grow.</quote>
	<quote id="333" author="Unknown">A negative mind will never give you a positive life.</quote>
	<quote id="334" author="flow">Never give up on the things that make you smile</quote>
	<quote id="335" author="Unknown">Everyone is beautiful on their own way. Don’t let the beauty standards of this era make you think otherwise.</quote>
	<quote id="336" author="Unknown">Just because you don't look like somebody who you think is attractive doesn't mean you aren't attractive. Flowers are pretty, but so are sunsets and they look nothing alike.</quote>
	<quote id="337" author="Unknown">It's never too late to start being who you want to be.</quote>
	<quote id="338" author="Unknown">It's never too late to change your life.</quote>
	<quote id="339" author="Unknown">How sweet it is to be loved by you</quote>
	<quote id="340" author="Unknown">Just because you took longer than others doesn't mean you failed.</quote>
	<quote id="341" author="Unknown">Keep growing</quote>
	<quote id="342" author="Unknown">Play your music loud and dance like an idiot</quote>
	<quote id="343" author="Unknown">Do one thing at a time, give it all your attention, honor it fully.</quote>
	<quote id="344" author="Unknown">Stop hating yourself for what you aren't and start loving yourself for what you are</quote>
	<quote id="345" author="Unknown">Love life and it will love you right back.</quote>
	<quote id="346" author="Neil Gaiman">You're alive. That means you have infinite potential. You can do anything, make anything, dream anything. If you change the world, the world will change.</quote>
	<quote id="347" author="Unknown">Make your heart the most beautiful thing about you.</quote>
	<quote id="348" author="Unknown">Make your happiness and personal growth a priority in your life. The more you take care of yourself, the more you can take care of others.</quote>
	<quote id="349" author="Unknown">Make yourself a priority.</quote>
	<quote id="350" author="Unknown">Today take some time to enjoy life's sweet and simple little pleasures.</quote>
	<quote id="351" author="Unknown">Be a light in this world</quote>
	<quote id="352" author="Unknown">Everyday is a fresh start.</quote>
	<quote id="353" author="Unknown">You do not need a mirror to know your beauty</quote>
	<quote id="354" author="Unknown">Je veux te rendre heureux(se)</quote>
	<quote id="355" author="Unknown">The people who want to stay in your life will always find a way</quote>
	<quote id="356" author="Unknown">Sometimes the advice you tell other people is the advice you need to follow</quote>
	<quote id="357" author="Unknown">Some days you just have to create your own sunshine</quote>
	<quote id="358" author="Unknown">Sometimes you have to fall before you can fly</quote>
	<quote id="359" author="Unknown">Never tell anyone your plans. Show them your results instead!</quote>
	<quote id="360" author="Unknown">The sky isn't the limit. Your vision is.</quote>
</quotes>
